

Contact

Address: New York, NY 10016 **Phone:** +1 (315) 636-4392

Mail:seriousman1994217winter@gmail.comGit:https://github.com/neymarjohnSkype:live:.cid.foo1faea3ab92d58

SKILLS

- Code and Quality Standards
- Database Management Software
- Project Management
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- JS Frameworks: React, Angular, Vue
- Code Analysis and Development
- Software Testing and Validation
- Programming Languages
- Source and Version Control: Git, Github
- Strong Interpersonal and Communication Skills
- Friendly, Positive Attitude
- Team Management

Neymar John

Skilled Senior Software Engineer designs and implements new features, improves architecture and takes lead to launch new products. Excellent understanding of software design and programming principles. Meaningful experience shipping and maintaining large, complex systems. Demonstrates hardworking and adaptable approach to challenges with strong analytical and critical thinking skills.

EXPERIENCE

Pinata, Omaha, Nebraska— Blockchain Developer

Mar 2021 - Oct 2022

- Maintained updated knowledge of emerging blockchain technologies and vendor products.
- Used object-oriented design principles and practices to create maintainable code base.
- Worked successfully with diverse group of coworkers to accomplish goals and address issues related to our products and services.

Zego, London - Software QA Engineer

Apr 2019 - Jun 2020

- Tested web application compatibility and performance to recommend crossbrowser compatibility improvements to web development team.
- Collaborated with developers, system installers and technical support representatives in identifying errors to determine appropriate team to consult for resolving issue.
- Developed delivery app(web and mobile) with team mates and supported

Sevenhillstechonology, Cincinnati — Senior Software Engineer

Mar 2016 - Nov 2018

- Tackled development tasks based on system requirements and documented approaches.
- Worked closely with development team members to identify and remove software bugs.
- Collaborated with development team members to create and integrate high availability solutions for mission-critical applications.
- Developed product and technology roadmap and strategy from concept to launch.
- Planned and created scalable and extensible systems for growing companies with intended expansion tracks.
- Designed mobile applications for Apple and Android platforms.
- Developed customized solutions for data pipelines using SWL and NoSQL data stores.

EDUCATION

Fordham University, Bronx, NY 10458, United States — *Bachelor of Science*

May 2009 - May 2013